Center for Technology in Government; Records ua433
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Center for Technology and Government1994-2013
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany. Center for Technology in Government
ua433
0.33 cubic ft. 19
Records of university-sponsored applied research center that examines and aids the adoption of technological innovation in government.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Administrative History
Founded in 1993, the Center for Technology in Government works with governmental agencies and corporate partners to improve the use of technology in government. The Center is funded from the University at Albany, SUNY, with the support of grants and awards from federal funding agencies. The Center supports the academic mission of the university by sponsoring courses and internships, working in particular with the Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy.
Scope and Contents
Collection includes the published annual reports of the Center for Technology in Government, available as digital objects.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection includes separate series for Web Archives and Annual Reports.
Acquisition Information
Annual Reports were collected from the Center for Technology in Government website using automated scripts. 2015 February
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Technology--Study and teaching.; Technology and State.; Web Archives; Digital Files; UAlbany Centers & Institutes; State University of New York at Albany. Center for Technology in Government
- Web Archives, 1997 January 6-2016 September 28; 1; 2151 captures
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service. This page includes links to both the university's collection and the Internet Archive's public collection.
  Surface-level crawling of www.albany.edu is performed daily which should includes most top-level webpages. Separate targeted crawls of every albany.edu subdomain are performed monthly to attempt to gather all content. This includes: www.albany.edu, www.rna.albany.edu, www.ctg.albany.edu, www.ualbanysports.com, www.albany.edu/rockefeller, www.albany.edu/cela, www.albany.edu/asrc, m.albany.edu, library.albany.edu, events.albany.edu, cstar.cestm.albany.edu, csda.albany.edu, and alumni.albany.edu
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Web Archives
  - https://www.ctg.albany.edu/ - University Archives collection, 2012 December 17-2016 September 28 (Web-archive 1)
  - WARC file for https://www.ctg.albany.edu/, (please see https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_ARChive for more details), 2012 December 17-2016 September 28 (Warc 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in researching with web archives.
  - https://www.ctg.albany.edu/ - Internet Archive collection, 1997 January 6-2016 September 28 (Web-archive 2)
- Annual Reports, 1994-2013; 2; 19
  - 1994 Annual Report, 1994 July 1; 321.08 KB (Pdf 1)
  - 1995 Annual Report, 1995 July 1; 365.57 KB (Pdf 2)
  - 1996 Annual Report, 1996 July 1; 825.13 KB (Pdf 3)
  - 1997 Annual Report, 1997 July 1; 387.23 KB (Pdf 4)
  - 1998 Annual Report, 1998 July 1; 759.59 KB (Pdf 5)
  - 1999 Annual Report, 1999 July 1; 875.81 KB (Pdf 6)
  - 2000 Annual Report, 2000 July 1; 492.95 KB (Pdf 7)
  - 2001 Annual Report, 2001 July 1; 887.81 KB (Pdf 8)
  - 2002 Annual Report, 2002 July 1; 577.85 KB (Pdf 9)
  - 2003 Annual Report, 2003 July 1; 2.92 MB (Pdf 10)
  - 2004 Annual Report, 2004 July 1; 401.96 KB (Pdf 11)
  - 2005 Annual Report, 2005 July 1; 389.35 KB (Pdf 12)
  - 2006 Annual Report, 2006 July 1; 750.91 KB (Pdf 13)
  - 2007 Annual Report, 2007 July 1; 325.36 KB (Pdf 14)
  - 2008 Annual Report, 2009 July 24; 497.66 KB (Pdf 15)
  - 2009 Annual Report, 2010 August 6; 1.84 MB (Pdf 16)
  - 2010 Annual Report, 2011 September 6; 1.32 MB (Pdf 17)
  - 2011 Annual Report, 2012 September 17; 1.5 MB (Pdf 18)
  - 2012 Annual Report, 2013 November 15; 3.17 MB (Pdf 19)